<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>CSH for tx_dam table</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<fileId>EXT:dam/locallang_csh_dam.xml</fileId>
		<csh_table>tx_dam</csh_table>
		<keep_original_text>1</keep_original_text>
		<labelContext type="array">
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index=".description">Meta data for media files.</label>
			<label index=".details">Media files can be attributed with meta information. Such information can describe the content (description, keywords, location), provide technical data (image size) or copyright information for example.
All these information can be used to handle, find and categorize the media files.</label>
			<label index="title.description">Title of document</label>
			<label index="title.details">The title of the media item will be displayed in list and item views. Please choose a short descriptive name, not including the type of item.</label>
			<label index="language.description">Language of the files content.</label>
			<label index="language.details"></label>
			<label index="abstract.description">Abstract of the files content.</label>
			<label index="abstract.details">The abstract is an automatically created excerpt of the files content or manually edited and should give an overview about the content.</label>
			<label index="creator.description">Photographer, editor, ....</label>
			<label index="creator.details">Could hold information about which person created the file. i.e. Photographer ...</label>
			<label index="ident.description"></label>
			<label index="ident.details">Could hold information like product number. This is for custom use and has no predefined format.</label>
			<label index="file_dl_name.description"></label>
			<label index="file_dl_name.details">A file name which should be used to download the file in a potential frontend application.</label>
			<label index="mime_type.description"></label>
			<label index="mime_type.details">A mime type describes the type of a file and is widely used in internet applications like email and www. Example: image/jpeg.</label>
			<label index="file_type.description"></label>
			<label index="file_type.details">Holds the file type, normally the file suffix.</label>
			<label index="file_creator.description">Program that created the file</label>
			<label index="file_creator.details">Holds information about the program used to create the file. i.e. Acrobat Distiller.</label>
			<label index="file_type_version.description">File format version</label>
			<label index="file_type_version.details">This is the version of the file format. For PDF 1.3 it is "1.3"</label>
			<label index="file_usage.description">Usage of the media item</label>
			<label index="file_usage.details">Display of the content elements in which the record is used.</label>
			<label index="pages.description">Number of pages of a document</label>
			<label index="pages.details"></label>
			<label index="date_cr.description">Creation date of the files content</label>
			<label index="date_cr.details">Can hold information about the creation of a file independent of the creation of the actual document on the server. Example: the date on which a photo was taken as opposed to the date on which the actual jpg-document was scanned.</label>
			<label index="date_mod.description">Date of the files content modification</label>
			<label index="date_mod.details">Can hold information about the changedate of a file independent of the changedate of the actual document on the server. Example: the date on which a digital artwork was modified as opposed to the date on which the actual document was saved last.</label>
			<label index="loc_desc.description"></label>
			<label index="loc_desc.details">Example: description where a photo was taken.</label>
			<label index="loc_country.description"></label>
			<label index="loc_country.details">Example: the country where a photo was taken.</label>
			<label index="loc_city.description"></label>
			<label index="loc_city.details">Example: the city where a photo was taken.</label>
			<label index="file_orig_location.description">Location of the original file like a photo CD name</label>
			<label index="file_orig_location.details">The file used here might be converted to a usable format (downscaled). This field can hold information where the original file resides. i.e. "Groovy Photos CD 3"</label>
			<label index="file_orig_loc_desc.description"></label>
			<label index="file_orig_loc_desc.details">This is a description of the location the original file can be found.</label>
		</languageKey>
        <languageKey index="de" type="array">
           <label index="title.description">Dokumententitel</label>
        </languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>